LUKE BAILEY

Location: Midlands

Email: lukejbailey2014@gmail.com

Portfolio: whiskerz1337.github.io/Portfolio

ABOUT ME

I am a friendly, focused, and inquisitive Cybersecurity Graduate recently back from Australia. I aim to leverage both my strong customer service experience and my technical expertise to provide swift and effective solutions to clients.

On a more personal level, I love gaming, I speak Spanish as a second language, and have been a self-taught guitarist for over 20 years.

TECHNICAL SKILLS SUMMARY

Operating Systems: Linux, Windows CLIs: Unix, Windows, Cisco IOS

Languages: JavaScript, Python, Bash, Dev Ops: Git, GitHub, Docker

Rust

Cybersecurity: Incident Response, Risk Other Skills: Project Management,

Assessments, Vulnerability Scanning Strong Communication, Pair

Programming

EDUCATION

PEN-200 (OSCP) Offensive Security August 2023 - Present Advanced Cert (AU) Cybersecurity August 2022 - July 2023 Cert IV (AU) Cybersecurity August 2021 - June 2022 BSc (Hons) 2.2 Music Technology 2010 - 2014

EMPLOYMENT

Sales, Service TTM

1800GJ (AU) February 2020 - August 2023

Direct Line GroupEVO consultant

January 2019 - December 2019

Direct Line Group January 2017 - December 2018

Landlord & Tradesmen Consultant